<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.audio.soundcloud" name="SoundCloud" version="2.0.6" provider-name="bromix">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
		<provides>audio</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="bg">SoundCloud е платформа за разпространяване на аудио.</summary>
		<summary lang="en">SoundCloud is an online audio distribution platform.</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Soundcloud ist ein Online-Audio-Vertriebsplattform.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">SoundCloud est une plateforme de streaming audio en ligne.</summary>
		<summary lang="he">סאונדקלאוד הוא פלטפורמת הפצת אודיו באינטרנט.</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">SoundCloud is een online audio distributie platform.</summary>
		<description lang="bg">SoundCloud е платформа за разпространение на аудио, която позволява на потребителите да качват, записват, представят и споделят звуците създадени от тях.</description>
		<description lang="en">SoundCloud is an online audio distribution platform that enables its users to upload, record, promote and share their originally-created sounds.</description>
		<description lang="de">Soundcloud ist ein Online-Audio-Vertriebsplattform. Benutzer können ihre ursprünglich erstelle Music hochladen, aufnehmen und unter weiteren Benutzern teilen.</description>
		<description lang="fr">SoundCloud est une plateforme de streaming audio en ligne qui permet aux utilisateurs d'envoyer, d'enregistrer, de promouvoir et partager leurs créations audio originales.</description>
		<description lang="he">סאונדקלאוד הוא פלטפורמה הפצת אודיו מקוונת המאפשרת למשתמשים שלה להעלות, להקליט, לקדם ולשתף את היצירות שלהם.</description>
		<description lang="nl">SoundCloud is een online audio distributie platform dat gebruikers in staat stelt om hun eigen muziekcreaties te uploaden, opnemen, promoten en te delen.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU General Public License v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=206635</forum>
		<website>www.soundcloud.com</website>
		<email>kodi at bromix dot org</email>
		<source>https://github.com/bromix/plugin.audio.soundcloud</source>
	</extension>
</addon>
