<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.cinetree" name="Cinetree" version="1.2.1" provider-name="Dimitri Kroon">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="19.0.5"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.31.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.6.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.codequick" version="1.0.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pytz" version="2023.3.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Films and documentaries from Cinetree.nl (Benelux countries only, account required)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Films en documentaires van Cinetree.nl (Alleen in de Benelux, account vereist)</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">
      This add-on enables playing films and documentaries from Dutch film platform Cinetree.[CR]This an unofficial addon. It is not created or endorsed by Cinetree.[CR][CR]To be able to play any content a Cinetree account is required. Films available in the monthy subscription account can be played directly from kodi. You can also browse through the whole rental collection.[CR]Just like the official TV-apps, it's not possible to rent a film directly from this addon. In order to watch a rental film you first have to make the payment via Cinetree's website or the official Cinetree Android/Apple app. Once paid the film will be available in the menu 'My Films' > 'Rented' for the duration of the rental period, which is usually 48 hours.
    </description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">
      Met deze addon kunnen films en documentaires worden afgespeeld van het Nederlandse filmplatform Cinetree.[CR]Dit is een onofficiële addon. Het is niet gemaakt of goedgekeurd door Cinetree.[CR][CR]Een Cinetree-account is vereist om films af te spelen. Films die beschikbaar zijn binnen het maand abonnement kan je direct bekijken en je kan het hele assortiment aan huurfilms doorzoeken.[CR]Net zoals met de officiële TV-apps kan je films niet direct huren vanuit deze addon. Om een huurfilm te kunnen bekijken moet je eerst betalen via de Cinetree-website of de officiële Cinetree Android/Apple app. Zodra er betaald is, is de film beschikbaar in het menu 'Mijn Films' > 'Gehuurd' voor de duur van de huurperiode, wat doorgaans 48 uur is.
    </description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">
      This addon is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
    </disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">
      Deze addon is gedistribueerd in de hoop dat het nuttig zal zijn maar ZONDER ENIGE GARANTIE; zelfs zonder de impliciete garantie voor BRUIKBAARHEID VOOR EEN SPECIFIEK DOEL.
    </disclaimer>
    <language>nl</language>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=370761</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/dimkroon/cinetree-for-kodi</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <news>
- Fix: Listings of subscription films failed with error Not Found.
- Some other minor issues.
    </news>
  </extension>
</addon>
