<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.aktualnetv" version="1.4.1" name="Aktualne TV" provider-name="Petr Kutalek">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
  </requires>

  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>

  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">This addon provides access to videos published on Aktualne TV</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Tento doplněk zpřístupňuje videa publikovaná na Aktuálně TV</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Tento doplnok sprístupňuje videa publikovaná na Aktuálně TV</summary>
    <description lang="en">Aktualne.cz — covering all aspects of life in the Czech Republic, from political, social, economic and sports news to arts and culture</description>
    <description lang="cs">Aktuálně.cz — kompletní zpravodajství, zprávy z domova i ze světa</description>
    <description lang="sk">Aktuálně.cz — kompletné spravodajstvo, správy z domova i zo sveta</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en">This is an unofficial addon and is in no way affiliated with publisher Economia, a. s. It was created and is maintained by an independent developer. It is provided for reference only and may contain errors.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">Toto je neoficiální doplněk a není, žel, žádným způsobem spojen s vydavatelstvím Economia, a. s. Byl vytvořen a je udržovan nezávislým vývojářem. Doplněk je poskytnut pouze jako ukázka a může obsahovat chyby.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk">Toto je neoficiálny doplnok a nie je, žiaľ, žiadnym spôsobom spojený s vydavateľstvom Economia, a. s. Bol vytvorený a je udržiavaný nezávislým vývojárom. Doplnok je poskytnutý len ako ukážka a môže obsahovať chyby.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language>cs</language>

    <license>GPL 2, June 1991</license>
    <website>https://video.aktualne.cz/</website>
    <forum>https://github.com/petrkutalek/plugin.video.aktualnetv/issues</forum>
    <email>petr@kutalek.cz</email>
    <source>https://github.com/petrkutalek/plugin.video.aktualnetv/</source>

    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-1.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-2.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-3.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-4.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>

    <news><![CDATA[Changelog:

[B]1.4.1[/B]
— Add SK translation and language resources
— Update screenshots (made on Kodi v17 now)
— Does not switch layout for shows now
— addon.py renamed to default.py for better compatibility
— Add support for live streams playback

[B]1.3.3[/B]
— Fixed name, stripped accents etc. — Kodi web is unable to handle it correctly

[B]1.3.2[/B]
— Fixed compatibility for Kodi v16/v17

[B]1.3.1[/B]
— Fixed JSON parsing, now it is more robust and tolerant

[B]1.2.3 — 1.2.4[/B]
— Fixed missing Shows thumbnail issue

[B]1.2.2[/B]
— Build for Kodi v17
]]></news>

  </extension>
</addon>
