<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.nederland24" name="Nederland 24" version="4.1.1" provider-name="bosel">
  <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="nederland24.py">
      <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">Dutch Public Broadcasting - Digital Channels and News Broadcasts</summary>
      <summary lang="nl">Digitale kanalen en Journaaluitzendingen van de Publieke Omroep</summary>
      <description lang="en">Dutch public broadcasting offers a number of digital theme channels available on Nederland 24. These specialized public broadcasting channels supply specific target audiences with thematic programming 24 hours a day. These channels provide more in-depth, broader and supplementary content that cannot be found on the three regular public channels. Dutch viewers decide for themselves on Nederland 24.</description>
      <description lang="nl">De publieke omroep biedt het Nederlandse publiek een aantal digitale themakanalen gebundeld in Nederland 24. Door middel van gespecialiseerde kanalen kan de publieke omroep specifieke doelgroepen 24 uur per dag van een thematische programmering voorzien. Het aanbod op deze kanalen vormt een verdieping, verbreding, aanvulling en/of versterking van reguliere uitzendingen en speelt in op het veranderende mediagedrag van het publiek. Het Nederlandse publiek kiest zelf wat het kijkt op Nederland 24.</description>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <language>nl en</language>
      <license>GPLv3</license>
      <forum></forum>
      <website>https://github.com/bosel/plugin.video.nederland24</website>
      <email></email>
      <source>https://github.com/bosel/plugin.video.nederland24</source>
      <disclaimer lang="en">Copyright 2011-2014 bosel.This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version. This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.</disclaimer>
  </extension>
</addon>