<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.tv3play.dk" version="3.1.0" name="TV3 Play" provider-name="anorm">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.buggalo" version="1.1.6"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="be">Watch the latest shows from TV3 Play and Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="ca">Mireu els darrers programes de TV3 Play i Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="da">Se de seneste udsendelser fra TV3 Play og Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Zeige die letzten Shows von TV3 Play und Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Παρακολουθήστε τις πιο πρόσφατες εκπομπές από το TV3 Play και το Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Watch the latest shows from TV3 Play and Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Mira los últimos programas de TV3 Play y Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Regarder les derniers shows depuis TV3 Play et Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">Ver os últimos programas de TV3 Play e Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="he">צפה בתוכניות האחרונות מ-TV3 Play ו-Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Gledajte najnovije serije sa TV3 Play i Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Nézze meg a legfrissebb műsorokat a TV3 Play és Viasat 4 Play oldalakról</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Guarda gli ultimi show da TV3 Play e Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">TV3 Play와 Viasat4 Play의 최근 쇼 감상</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Žiūrėti naujausius laidas iš TV3Play ir Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="no">Se de nyeste episodene fra TV3 Play og Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Oglądaj najnowsze programy z TV3 Play oraz Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">Veja os últimos programas de TV3 Play e Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Assista os últimos shows de TV3 Play e Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="sk">Sledujte najaktuálnejšie vysielanie z TV3 Play a Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Titta på dom senaste serierna från TV3 Play och Viasat 4 Play</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">观看TV3 Play和Viasat 4 Play最新节目</summary>
        <description lang="be">On TV3 Play you can watch all of TV3's own programming and some foreign series. There is also extra feature for some programming.</description>
        <description lang="ca">A TV3 Play podeu veure tota la programació pròpia de TV3 i algunes sèries estrangeres. Hi ha també extres d'alguns programes.</description>
        <description lang="da">På TV3 Play kan du se alle TV3's egne programmer og nogle udenlandske serier. Der er også ekstramateriale til flere af programmerne.</description>
        <description lang="de">Auf TV3 Play kannst du alle TV3 Programme und einige ausländische Serien sehen. Außerdem gibt es für einige Programme extra funktionen. </description>
        <description lang="el">Στο TV3 Play μπορείτε να παρακολουθήσετε όλο το πρόγραμμά του καθώς και κάποιες ξένες σειρές. Υπάρχουν, επίσης, επιπλέον λειτουργίες για κάποια προγράμματα.</description>
        <description lang="en">On TV3 Play you can watch all of TV3's own programming and some foreign series. There is also extra feature for some programming.</description>
        <description lang="es">En TV3 Play puedes ver todos los programas de TV3 y algunas series extranjeras. También hay características especiales para algunos programas.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Sur TV3 Play vous pouvez regarder tous les programmes de TV3 et quelques séries étrangères. Il y a aussi une fonctionnalité supplémentaire pour quelques programmes.</description>
        <description lang="gl">En TV3 Play pode ver toda a programación da canle e algunhas series extranxeiras, mais tamén características adicionais nalgunha programación.</description>
        <description lang="he">ב-TV3 Play הינך יכול לצפות בכל תוכניות TV3 ובסדרות זרות נוספות. לתוכניות מסויימות קיימת יכולות נוספות.</description>
        <description lang="hr">Na TV3 Play možete gledati sav program koji je u vlasništvu TV3's i neke strane serije. Postoje i dodatne značajke za neke programe.</description>
        <description lang="hu">A TV3 Play-en saját műsorokat és külföldi sorozatokat nézhet.  címen</description>
        <description lang="it">Con TV3Play puoi guardare tutta la programmazione di TV3 e qualche altra serie. Ci sono anche funzionalità extra per alcuni palinsesti.</description>
        <description lang="ko">On TV3 Play you can watch all of TV3's own programming and some foreign series. There is also extra feature for some programming.</description>
        <description lang="lt">TV3 Play priede galite žiūrėti visas TV3 savo šalies ir kai kurias užsienio laidas. Taip pat yra papildoma programos funkcija</description>
        <description lang="no">På TV3 Play kan du se alle av TV3s egne programmer og noen utenlanske serier. Det finnes også tilleggsfunksjoner til noen av programmene.</description>
        <description lang="pl">Na TV3 Play możesz oglądać wszystkie własne programy TV3 oraz kilka zagranicznych serii. Istnieje równierz dodatkowa funkcje dla niektórych programów.</description>
        <description lang="pt">Com o TV3 Play, pode ver toda a programação própria da TV3 e ainda algumas séries estrangeiras. Tem também mais funcionalidades para alguma programação.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Na TV3 você pode assistir toda a programação da própria TV3 e algumas séries estrangeiras. Há também recursos extras para alguma programação. </description>
        <description lang="sk">Na TV3 Play môžete sledovať všetku vlastnú tvorbu TV3 a niektoré zahraničné seriály. K dispozícii je tiež extra funkcie pre niektoré programy.</description>
        <description lang="sv">På TV3 Play kan du se alla TV3's egna program samt några utländska serier. Det finns också extra funktioner för några av programmen.</description>
        <description lang="zh">在TV3 Play你可以观看TV3全部自有和国外系列节目，还有一些节目的附加内容。</description>
        <disclaimer lang="be">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ca">Algunes parts d'aquest afegitó podrien ser il·legals al vostre pais de residència - per favor, comprovau les vostres lleis locals.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="da">Nogle dele af denne addon er muligvis ikke lovlige i dit land - kontroller venligst dine lokale love.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de">Einige Teile dieses Addons sind eventuell nicht in deinem derzeitigen Land legal - bitte überprüfe deine lokalen Gesetze.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el">Κάποια τμήματα αυτού του πρόσθετου ενδέχεται να μην είναι νόμιμα στη χώρα σας - ελέγξτε τη νομοθεσία σας.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Algunas partes de este complemento pueden no ser legales en tu país de residencia. Por favor comprueba la legalidad vigente.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr">Certaines parties de cette extension ne sont peut-être pas légales dans votre pays - veuillez vérifier avec vos lois locales.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="gl">Algunhas partes deste engadido poden non ser legais no teu país - por favor verifica as leis locais.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="he">יתכן שחלקים מסוימים בהרחבה זו אינם חוקיים במדינתך - אנא ודא זאת מול הרשויות המתאימות.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hr">Neki dijelovi ovog dodatka možda nisu legalni u vašoj zemlji ili prebivalištu - provjerite vaše lokalne zakone prije instaliranja.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hu">A kiegészítő néhány részlete illegális lehet az ön országában - kérjük nézzen utána a törvényeknek.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it">Alcune parti di questo addon potrebbero non essere legali nel tuo paese di residenza - per favore controlla le leggi vigenti.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ko">이 애드온의 일부는 거주하는 국가에 따라 합법적이지 않을 수도 있습니다. 이용 지역의 법률을 확인하세요.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="lt">Kai kurios šio priedo dalys negali būti naudojamos/vartojamos/žiūrimos jūsų šalyje - prašome patikrinti gyvenamosios vietos įstatymus.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="no">Det kan hende at noen deler av dette tillegget ikke er lovelige i ditt land - vennligst sjekk med dine lokale lover.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl">Niektóre części tej wtyczki moga być nielegalne w twoim kraju  - proszę sprawdzić z lokalnymi przepisami.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt">Algumas partes deste addon podem não ser legais no seu país de residência - por favor, verifique a legislação local.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Algumas partes desta addon pode não ser legais em seu país - por favor verifique as leis locais, antes de usar.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sk">Niektoré časti tohoto doplnku môžu byť protizákonné vo Vašej krajine pobytu - prosím informujte sa o miestnych zákonoch.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">Några delar i detta tillägg kanske inte är lagligt i ditt hemland - var god kontrollera med dom lokala lagarna.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh">这个插件的某些内容可能不符合你所在国家的法律规定 - 请确认符合当地法律。</disclaimer>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <language>da se no lt lv ee bg</language>
        <website>https://github.com/anorm/plugin.video.tv3play.dk</website>
        <email>anders@norman.info</email>
        <source>https://github.com/anorm/plugin.video.tv3play.dk</source>
    </extension>
</addon>
