<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<strings>
	<string id="30001">General</string>
	<string id="30002">Channel Genres</string>
	<string id="30010">Preferred Quality</string>
	<string id="30011">Prefer SD</string>
	<string id="30012">Prefer HD</string>
	<string id="30013">Show SD &amp; HD</string>
	<string id="30020">Preferred Channel Image</string>
	<string id="30021">Poster</string>
	<string id="30022">Thumbnail</string>
	<string id="30030">Network Categories</string>
	<string id="30031">Only Public Networks</string>
	<string id="30032">Only Commercial Networks</string>
	<string id="30033">All</string>
	<string id="30040">Hierarchical Menu</string>
	<string id="30080">General Channels</string>
	<string id="30081">Regional Channels</string>
	<string id="30082">Cultural Channels</string>
	<string id="30083">Special Interest Channels</string>
	<string id="30084">News Channels</string>
	<string id="30090">General Channel</string>
	<string id="30091">Regional Channel</string>
	<string id="30092">Cultural Channel</string>
	<string id="30093">Special Interest Channel</string>
	<string id="30094">News Channel</string>
	<string id="30101">Das Erste ("The First"), rarely also called Erstes Deutsches Fernsehen ("First German Television"), is the principal publicly owned television channel in Germany. It is a joint production of Germany's regional public broadcasters acting through, and coordinated by the ARD consortium.</string>
	<string id="30102">Zweites Deutsches Fernsehen (English: "Second German Television"), ZDF, is a public-service German television broadcaster based in Mainz (Rheinland-Pfalz). It is run as an independent non-profit institution, which was founded by all federal states of Germany (Bundesländer). ZDF is financed by television licence fees and advertising revenues.</string>
	<string id="30103">Bayerischer Rundfunk (Bavarian Broadcasting, BR) is public-service radio and television broadcaster, based in Munich, capital city of the Free State of Bavaria in Germany. BR is a member organization of the ARD consortium of public broadcasters in Germany.</string>
	<string id="30104">Mitteldeutscher Rundfunk (Central German Broadcasting, MDR) is the public broadcaster for the federal states of Thuringia, Saxony and Saxony-Anhalt. Established in January 1991, it has its headquarters in Leipzig and regional studios in Dresden, Erfurt and Magdeburg. MDR broadcasts its own television channel to the three states it serves and contributes to the first German TV channel (Das Erste) and also broadcasts various radio channels.</string>
	<string id="30105">Norddeutscher Rundfunk (NDR) (North German Broadcasting) is a public radio and television broadcaster, based in Hamburg. In addition to the city-state of Hamburg, NDR transmits for the German states of Lower Saxony, Mecklenburg-Vorpommern and Schleswig-Holstein. NDR is a member of the ARD consortium.</string>
	<string id="30106">Radio Bremen (RB), Germany's smallest public radio and television broadcaster, is the legally mandated broadcaster for the city-state Free Hanseatic City of Bremen (which includes Bremerhaven). With its headquarters sited in Bremen, Radio Bremen is a member of the consortium of German public broadcasting organizations, ARD.</string>
	<string id="30107">Rundfunk Berlin-Brandenburg (rbb) (Berlin-Brandenburg Broadcasting) is an institution under public law (national broadcaster) for the German states of Berlin and Brandenburg, situated in Berlin and Potsdam. rbb was established on 1 May 2003 through the merger of Sender Freies Berlin (SFB) and Ostdeutscher Rundfunk Brandenburg (ORB), based in Potsdam, and is a member of the Association of PSBs in the Federal Republic of Germany (ARD).</string>
	<string id="30108">Saarländischer Rundfunk (Saarland Broadcasting - SR) is a public radio and television broadcaster for the German Bundesland (State) of Saarland, with its headquarters in the Broadcasting House Halberg in Saarbrücken. SR is a member of the ARD.</string>
	<string id="30109">Südwestrundfunk (SWR, "Southwest Broadcasting") is a regional public broadcasting corporation serving the southwest of Germany, specifically the federal states of Baden-Württemberg and Rhineland-Palatinate. The corporation has main offices in three cities: Stuttgart, Baden-Baden and Mainz, with the director's office being in Stuttgart. It is a part of the ARD consortium.</string>
	<string id="30110">Westdeutscher Rundfunk (WDR, West German Broadcasting) is a German public-broadcasting institution based in the Federal State of North Rhine-Westphalia with its main office in Cologne. WDR is a constituent member of the consortium of German public-broadcasting institutions, ARD. As well as contributing to the output of national television channel Das Erste, WDR produces the regional television service WDR Fernsehen (formerly known as WDF and West3) and six regional radio networks.</string>
	<string id="30111">3sat is a public, advertising-free, television network in Central Europe. The programming is in German (in either Standard German or Austrian Standard German, depending on the producer of the programme) and is aimed primarily at audiences in Germany, Austria and Switzerland (the major countries of the German-speaking world).</string>
	<string id="30112">Arte (Association Relative à la Télévision Européenne) is a Franco-German TV network, a European channel, that promotes programming in the areas of culture and the arts. It is made up of three separate companies: the Strasbourg based European Economic Interest Grouping Arte GEIE plus two member companies acting as editorial and programme production centres, Arte France in Paris (France) and Arte Deutschland in Baden-Baden (Germany). As an international joint venture (an EEIG), its programs cater technically to audiences from both France and Germany.</string>
	<string id="30113">EinsFestival programming includes documentaries, magazine programmes, films and music (rock and classical). Most of the programmes have already been broadcast by other public stations that belong to the ARD.</string>
	<string id="30114">ZDFkultur is a digital TV channel, run by ZDF. It was launched on 7 May 2011, replacing ZDFtheaterkanal. It mainly broadcasts music shows, such as "Later..." with Jools Holland, pop concerts and series from the ZDF archive, but also movies and plays.</string>
	<string id="30115">KiKA (Der KinderKAnal von ARD und ZDF  [The Children's Channel of ARD and ZDF]) is a free, public, non-commercial television channel based in Erfurt, Germany. Its channel designation was formerly KI.KA.</string>
	<string id="30116">Phoenix is a publicly funded television station in Germany which is produced jointly by public broadcasting organizations ARD and ZDF. Its programming consists of documentaries, news broadcasts, special events coverage, and discussion programmes. Phoenix's headquarters are in the former West German capital, Bonn.</string>
	<string id="30117">BR-alpha is a German television station owned by regional broadcaster Bayerischer Rundfunk. BR-alpha broadcasts educational programmes including; science, religion, music, philosophy, literature, art and culture.</string>
	<string id="30118">EinsPlus is a digital television channel from the German broadcaster ARD and managed by ARD regional broadcaster SWR. The channel launched on 29 August 1997 under the name EinsMuXx, and was renamed EinsPlus on 23 April 2005.</string>
	<string id="30119">	</string>
	<string id="30120">DW-TV is a set of television channels provided by Deutsche Welle. The channels concentrate on news and information and first started broadcasting 1 April 1992. The channels are broadcast on satellite and produced in Berlin.</string>
	<string id="30121">Tagesschau24 is a digital television channel produced by the German broadcaster ARD and mananged by the Hamburg-based ARD regional broadcaster NDR. It launched on 30 August 1997 as "EinsExtra" before the introduction on its current name on 1 May 2012.</string>
	<string id="30122">ZDFinfo is a digital TV channel from ZDF. It was launched on 27 August 1997 as ZDFinfokanal.</string>
	<string id="30123">ZDFneo is a German digital terrestrial television channel, programmed for an audience aged 18 to 45 to counter the primarily older-skewing main channels of public broadcasters ZDF and ARD. It replaced ZDF's documentary channel, "ZDFdokukanal", on November 1, 2009.</string>
	<string id="30124">Hessischer Rundfunk (Hessian Broadcasting) (HR) is the public broadcaster for the German state (Bundesland) of Hesse. The main offices of HR are in Frankfurt am Main. HR is a member of the ARD. Since December 2013 the channel is also available in HDTV.</string>
	<string id="30125">	</string>
	<string id="30126">	</string>
	<string id="30127">	</string>
	<string id="30128">	</string>
	<string id="30129">	</string>
	<string id="30130">RTL Television (formerly RTL plus), or simply RTL, is a German commercial television station distributed via cable and satellite, as well as via digital terrestrial (DVB-T) in more highly populated areas. It is owned by the RTL Group and is, in terms of market share, Germany's largest private free-to-air broadcaster.</string>
	<string id="30131">VOX or Vox is a German television channel, headquartered in Cologne and part of the RTL Group, Europe's second largest TV, radio, and production company. The channel officially launched at 5:00pm on January 25, 1993. Prior to that, test transmissions had been made using the informal name Westschienenkanal (West slot channel, a reference to Nordschienenkanal and Südschienenkanal, the informal names used in the 1980s for the other two German private channels RTL Television and Sat.1). The channel mainly broadcasts documentaries and U.S. series and movies.</string>
	<string id="30132">RTL II is a commercial, privately owned, general-interest German television channel. In 2012 the channel had a market share of 4% among viewers aged over three.</string>
	<string id="30133">Super RTL is a Cologne-based German television network operated by RTL Disney Fernsehen GmbH &amp; Co. KG. It was the second German television channel aimed mostly at children (the first was Nickelodeon and Cartoon Network). It was launched in 1995 as a joint venture between RTL Group predecessor company Compagnie Luxembourgeoise de Télédiffusion and The Walt Disney Company.</string>
	<string id="30134">n-tv is a German television news channel owned by the Bertelsmann AG Media's RTL Group and an affiliate network of CNN since the networks creation in 1992. n-tv screens news bulletins on the hour and half hour; in between, it broadcasts informational programmes and advertising.</string>
	<string id="30135">	</string>
	<string id="30136">	</string>
	<string id="30137">	</string>
	<string id="30138">	</string>
	<string id="30139">	</string>
</strings>
