<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.audio.somafm"
       name="SomaFM"
       version="2.0.1"
       provider-name="Soma-FM-Kodi-Add-On Organization">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Listener supported radio</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Hörergetragenes Radio</summary>
        <summary lang="nl_NL">Luisteraarondersteunde Radio</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Over 30 unique channels of listener-supported, commercial-free, underground/alternative radio broadcasting from San Francisco. All music hand-picked by SomaFM's award-winning DJs and music directors.
        Please consider donating at https://somafm.com to keep this service alive!</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Über 30 einzigartige Sender vom hörergetragenen, werbefreien, underground / alternative Radio aus San Francisco. Die gesamte Musik ist handerlesen von SomaFMs ausgezeichneten DJs und Musikprogrammleitern.
        Bitte denk über eine Spende auf https://somafm.com nach, um diesen Dienst am Leben zu halten!</description>
        <description lang="nl_NL">Meer dan 30 unieke kanalen van luisteraarondersteunde, reclamevrije, alternatieve radiouitzendingen uit San Fransisco. Alle muziek is handgeselecteerd door SomaFM's bekroonde dj's en muzikale programmamakers.
        Overweeg a.u.b. een donatie te doen op https://somafm.com om deze service   bin leven te houden!</description>
        <website>https://somafm.com</website>
        <source>https://github.com/Soma-FM-Kodi-Add-On/plugin.audio.somafm</source>
        <news>
        Version 2.0.1 - 2021-11-16
        - Updating details 
        - Implementing stability measures

        Version 2.0.0 - 2021-11-16
        - Update to Python3 
        - Updating to adhere to newish automated testing tool standards

        Version 1.1.0 - 2016-02-22
        - Remove firewall mode in response to the SomaFM streaming server update

        Version 1.0.2 - 2015-11-08
        - Dutch translation and some polishing by PanderMusubi - thanks!

        Version 1.0.1 - 2015-01-01
        - Fix playback on Android client

        Version 1.0.0 - 2014-10-09
        - Use localized strings, supporting English and German for now
        - Settings for caching the channel list and clearing the cache
        - Include a donation reminder ❤️

        Version 0.1.0 - 2014-10-05
        - Automatically select a stream and instantly start playback when station is selected
        - Cache playlist files
        - Settings for quality, format and firewall streams

        Version 0.0.2 - 2013-07-21
        - Use SomaFM XML API.

        Version 0.0.1 - 2011-03-07
        - Initial version.
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
