<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.drnu" version="5.0.13" name="DR TV" provider-name="TermeHansen">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests-cache" version="0.4.13"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
        <import addon="script.module.buggalo" version="1.1.2"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Watch live and archived TV from DR (Danish Broadcasting Corporation)</summary>
        <summary lang="da_DK">Se live og arkiveret TV fra DR</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">All DR's live TV channels and archived programs as seen on dr.dk/tv.[CR][CR]If you have comments or suggestions for this addon, please feel free to participate in the KODI official forums</description>
        <description lang="da_DK">Alle DR's live TV kanaler samt alle de programmer du finder på dr.dk/tv.[CR][CR]Har du kommentarer, ris eller ros til denne addon er du velkommen til at deltage i debatten på KODI forummet</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="da_DK">Nogle dele af denne addon er muligvis ikke lovlig i dit land - kontroller venligst dine lokale love.</disclaimer>
        <license>GPL 2.0</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <language>da</language>
        <email>termopeten@gmail.com</email>
        <website>https://www.dr.dk/</website>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/xbmc-danish-addons/plugin.video.drnu</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
       </assets>
       <news>[B]Version 5.0.13 - 2021-02-27[/B]
- Adding old PR's + minor fixes. last update before kodi 19 and python3
- Change for request-cache for storing web requests locally (in 8hours) #34
- Fix missing thumbnails and added option in settings to choose fan-art image size #29 #35
- Fixed themes menu item #34
- Add support for other plugins to start live tv. #31
- Update logos and entry screen #24
- Change subtitle handling to local srt files, so user also can change for hard-of-hearing subs and change while watching #36
    </news>
    </extension>
</addon>
