<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.program.remote.control.browser" name="Remote Control Browser" version="1.3.2" provider-name="Chad Parry">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.3.2"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Browse websites with a remote control</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Browse websites with a remote control</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Surfen auf Webseiten mit einer Fernbedienung</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Navegar em sites com um controle remoto</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">The most powerful way to access content on Netflix and YouTube and Amazon Instant Video would be a web browser, if web browsers provided good native support for a 10-foot user interface. This add-on launches a browser and connects the arrow buttons on the remote control to the mouse pointer. This is the most user-friendly way to consume online content without needing a wireless keyboard.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">The most powerful way to access content on Netflix and YouTube and Amazon Instant Video would be a web browser, if web browsers provided good native support for a 10-foot user interface. This add-on launches a browser and connects the arrow buttons on the remote control to the mouse pointer. This is the most user-friendly way to consume online content without needing a wireless keyboard.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Der beste Weg, um auf Inhalte auf Netflix und YouTube und Amazon Instant Video zuzugreifen wäre ein Webbrowser, wenn Webbrowser für eine 10-Fuß-Benutzeroberfläche gute native Unterstützung böten. Dieses Addon startet einen Browser und verbindet die Pfeiltasten auf der Fernbedienung mit dem Mauszeiger. Dies ist der benutzerfreundlichste Weg Online-Inhalte zu konsumieren, ohne eine drahtlose Tastatur zu benötigen.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">A forma mais poderosa de acessar o conteúdo no Netflix e YouTube e Amazon Instant Video seria um navegador web, se navegadores web fornecessem um bom suporte nativo para a interface de usuário de 10-foot. Este add-on inicia um navegador e conecta os botões de navigação do controle remoto para o ponteiro do mouse. Esta é a interface mais amigável para consumir conteúdo online sem a necessidade de um teclado sem fio.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">The experience will be degraded unless these external dependencies are installed: “psutil,” “pyalsaaudio,” “pylirc2,” and “Pillow.” Another helpful utility is “unclutter,” which automatically hides the mouse pointer. (On a Debian-based system, run “sudo apt-get install python-psutil python-alsaaudio python-pylirc python-pil unclutter”). Finally, a theme with a large mouse pointer will improve pointer visibility, (e.g., https://www.gnome-look.org/p/999574/).</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_US">The experience will be degraded unless these external dependencies are installed: “psutil,” “pyalsaaudio,” “pylirc2,” and “Pillow.” Another helpful utility is “unclutter,” which automatically hides the mouse pointer. (On a Debian-based system, run “sudo apt-get install python-psutil python-alsaaudio python-pylirc python-pil unclutter”). Finally, a theme with a large mouse pointer will improve pointer visibility, (e.g., https://www.gnome-look.org/p/999574/).</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Die Erfahrung wird vermindert werden, wenn nicht diese externen Abhängigkeiten installiert sind: „psutil“, „pyalsaaudio“, „pylirc2“ und „Pillow“. Ein weiteres hilfreiches Werkzeug ist „unclutter“, das automatisch den Mauszeiger versteckt. (Auf einem Debian-basierten System führen Sie „sudo apt-get install python-psutil python-alsaaudio python-pylirc python-pil unclutter“ aus). Schließlich wird ein Theme mit einem großen Mauszeiger die Sichtbarkeit verbessern, (zum Beispiel https://www.gnome-look.org/p/999574/).</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">A experiência será degradada, a menos que essas dependências externas estejam instaladas: “psutil”, “pyalsaaudio”, “pylirc2” e “Pillow”. Outra ferramenta útil é “unclutter”, que oculta automaticamente o ponteiro do mouse. (Em um sistema baseado em Debian, execute “sudo apt-get install python-psutil python-alsaaudio python-pylirc python-pil unclutter”). Finalmente, um tema com um ponteiro do mouse grande irá melhorar a visibilidade do ponteiro, (por exemplo, https://www.gnome-look.org/p/999574/).</disclaimer>
        <news>v1.3.0 (2018-11-23)
- Support PulseAudio</news>
        <platform>linux osx</platform>
        <language></language>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <forum></forum>
        <website>https://chad.parry.org/software/kodi/</website>
        <source>https://github.com/chadparry/kodi-plugin.program.remote.control.browser</source>
        <email>github at chad dot parry dot org</email>
    </extension>
</addon>
