<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.srf_ch_replay" name="Unofficial SRF Replay" version="2.0.2" provider-name="Man Behind MooN">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
	 <news>- Former "SRF Podcast Plugin" reloaded as "Unofficial SRF Replay" for Kodi 19
- New Logo and unofficial added to the name
- TV show navigation improved
[New] Fanart added with final design
[INFO] No new features will be added to this add-on (see disclaimer)
[INFO] A new add-on "Unofficial SRG SSR Replay" has been launched that supports all current and more features</news>
	<assets>
		<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
		<fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
	</assets>
    <summary lang="en_GB">The unofficial SRF Replay add-on plays TV shows from the SRF channel.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">The unofficial SRF Replay add-on streams recorded TV shows from the national Swiss German TV station SRF over the provided API. All the shows are mainly in German.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This add-on is not endorsed by SRG SSR and no support can be claimed. This add-on uses an unsupported API. This add-on is deprecated and will just be kept alive in its current state as long as the current used API is working. No new features will be added. A new version of this add-on "Unofficial SRG SSR Replay" has been launched that supports all the current features and some more.</disclaimer>
	<summary lang="de_DE">Das inoffizielle SRF Replay Add-on zeigt alle SRF Sendungen.</summary>
    <description lang="de_DE">Das inoffizielle SRF Replay Add-on zeigt aufgezeichneten Sendungen vom nationalen Schweizer deutschsprachigen TV Sender SRF über das zur Verfügung gestellte API. Die Sendungen sind hauptsächlich in deutscher Sprache.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Dieses Add-on ist nicht offiziell von der SRG SSR und es bestehen keinerlei Support-Ansprüche. Das Add-on benutzt eine nicht supportete Schnittstelle. Dieses Add-on ist am Lebensende angekommen und wird nur noch solange die jetzt benutzte Schnittstelle funktioniert am Leben erhalten. Keine neuen Funktionen werden hinzugefügt. Ein neues Add-on "Unofficial SRG SSR Replay" steht zur Verfügung mit allen jetzigen und mehr Funktionen.</disclaimer>
    <language>de</language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <email>man_behind_moon at gmx dot net</email>
    <source>https://github.com/ManBehindMooN/kodi_plugin_video_srf_ch_replay</source>
    <website>https://www.srf.ch/play</website>
  </extension>
</addon>