<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.audio.shoutcast" name="SHOUTcast 2" version="2.3.0" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
        <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.xmltodict" version="0.2.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>http://www.shoutcast.com/</website>
        <source>https://github.com/dersphere/plugin.audio.shoutcast</source>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=143678</forum>
        <email>sphere@dersphere.de</email>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <summary lang="ar">وجود اكثر من 50.000 محطة اذاعية مجانية على الانترنت </summary>
        <summary lang="be">more than 50.000 free internet radio stations</summary>
        <summary lang="bg">повече от 50 000 безплатни интернет радиостанции</summary>
        <summary lang="ca">Més de 50.000 estacions de ràdio per Internet gratuïtes</summary>
        <summary lang="da">mere end 50.000 gratis netradiostationer</summary>
        <summary lang="de">mehr als 50.000 kostenlose Internet Radio Sender</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Πάνω από 50.000 δωρεάν διαδικτυακοί ραδιοφωνικοί σταθμοί</summary>
        <summary lang="en">more than 50.000 free internet radio stations</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">more than 50.000 free internet radio stations</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">more than 50.000 free internet radio stations</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Más de 50.000 emisoras de radio por Internet gratuitas</summary>
        <summary lang="es_MX">mas de 50.000 estaciones de radio gratuitas</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">plus de 50.000 radios internet gratuites</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">plus de 50 000 stations de radio Internet gratuites</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">máis de 50.000 emisoras de radio por internet de balde</summary>
        <summary lang="he">יותר מ־50.000 תחנות רדיו אינטרנטיות חינמיות</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">više od 50.000 besplatnih Internet radio stanica</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Több mint 50.000 ingyenes internet rádió</summary>
        <summary lang="id">lebih dari 50.000 stasiun radio internet gratisan</summary>
        <summary lang="it">più di 50.000 stazioni radio libere su internet</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">50,000개 이상의 무료 인터넷 라디오 방송 청취</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">daugiau kaip 50,000 nemokamų internetinių radijo stočių</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Meer dan 50.000 vrije internet radio stations</summary>
        <summary lang="no">mer enn 50.000 gratis radiokanaler fra internett</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Ponad 50.000 darmowych internetowych stacji radiowych</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">mais de 50.000 estações de rádio da net grátis</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">mais de 50.000 estações de rádio gratuitas on-line</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">более 50 000 свободных интернет радиостанций</summary>
        <summary lang="sk">Viac než 50.000 voľných internetových rádio staníc</summary>
        <summary lang="sl">več kot 50000 brezplačnih internetnih radijskih postaj</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">mer än 50.000 fria internetradiostationer</summary>
        <summary lang="ta_IN">50.000 மேற்பட்ட இலவச இணைய வானொலி நிலையங்கள்</summary>
        <summary lang="tr">50.000 den Fazla Ücretsiz Internet Radyo Istasyonu</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">超过50.000免费网络电台</summary>
        <description lang="be">With this Add-on you can browse more than 50.000 free internet radio stations. Current Features:[CR]- Top 500 Stations[CR]- Browse by genre (and subgenre if enabled in settings)[CR]- Search Station by name[CR]- Search Stations by current playing track[CR]- You can manage a "My Stations"-list[CR]- bitrate and amount of listeners visible and sortable[CR]- 500 Stations on each Page (can be changed in the settings)[CR]- uses cache (24h genre, 1h station listings)</description>
        <description lang="bg">С това допълнение, можете да слушате над 50.000 достъпни и свободни радиостанции. В момента плъгина позволява:[CR] - Преглед на Топ 500 станции[CR] - Търсене по жанр (и поджанрове, ако е определено в настройките)[CR] - Търсене на станции по име[CR] - Търсене на подобни станции по текущо възпроизвежданата музика[CR] - Управление на списъка "Моите станции"[CR] - Преглеждане, сортиране по битрейт и количество слушатели[CR] - 500 станции на всяка страница (може да се промени в настройките)[CR] - Ползване на кеширане (стилове на 24 часа, списъци на станции на 1 час)</description>
        <description lang="ca">Amb aquest Add-on poden escoltar més de 50.000 emissores de ràdio per Internet gratuïtes. Característiques: [CR]- Les 500 millors emissores. [CR]- Cerca per gènere (i per subgèneres si s'habilita en la configuració). [CR]- Cerca d'emissores per nom. [CR]- Recerca d'emissores que reprodueixen una cançó. [CR]- Possibilitat d'administrar un directori amb "Els meus emissores". [CR]- Directoris ordenats que mostren bitrate i quantitat d'oients. [CR]- 500 emissores a cada pàgina (la quantitat pot canviar en la configuració). [CR]- Ús de memòria cau (24h gènere, 1h directori d'emissores).</description>
        <description lang="da">Med denne addon kan du udforske mere end 50.000 gratis internetradiostationer. Nuværende funktioner:[CR]- Top 500 Stationer[CR]- Gennemse efter genre (og undergenre hvis det er aktiveret i indstillinger)[CR]- Søg efter navn på Station[CR]- Søg efter Station ud fra nummeret der spiller[CR]- Du kan administrere en "My Stations"-liste[CR]- bitrate og antal lyttere vises og kan sorteres[CR]- 500 Stationer på hver side (kan ændres i indstillinger)[CR]- bruger cache (24 timer for genre, 1 time for lister)</description>
        <description lang="de">Dieses Add-on ermöglicht dir Zugriff auf über 50.000 kostenlose Internet Radio Sender.[CR]Aktuelle Features:[CR]- Top 500 Sender[CR]- Nach Genre browsen[CR]- Sender nach Name suchen[CR]- Sender nach aktuellem Track suchen[CR]- Sender per Kontext Menu in die "Meine Sender"-Liste kopieren[CR]- Anzeige der Bitrate und Anzahl Höhrer[CR]- 500 Sender pro Seite[CR]- Schnell durch lokalen Cache</description>
        <description lang="el">Με αυτό το Πρόσθετο μπορείτε να περιηγηθείτε ανάμεσα σε περισσότερους από 50.000 δωρεάν διαδικτυακούς ραδιοφωνικούς σταθμούς. Τρέχουσες λειτουργίες:[CR]- Κορυφαίοι 500 Σταθμοί[CR]- Περιήγηση ανά είδος (και υπο-είδος αν είναι ενεργό στις ρυθμίσεις)[CR]- Αναζήτηση Σταθμού με βάση το όνομα[CR]- Αναζήτηση Σταθμών με βάση το τρέχον τραγούδι[CR]- Μπορείτε να διαχειριστείτε μία λίστα "Σταθμών μου"[CR]- Το bitrate και το πλήθος των ακροατών είναι ορατά και η ταξινόμηση μπορεί να γίνει σύμφωνα με αυτά[CR]- 500 Σταθμοί σε κάθε Σελίδα (μπορεί να αλλάξει στις ρυθμίσεις)[CR]- Χρήση λανθάνουσας μνήμης (είδος 24 ωρών, καταχωρίσεις σταθμών 1 ώρας)</description>
        <description lang="en">With this Add-on you can browse more than 50.000 free internet radio stations. Current Features:[CR]- Top 500 Stations[CR]- Browse by genre (and subgenre if enabled in settings)[CR]- Search Station by name[CR]- Search Stations by current playing track[CR]- You can manage a "My Stations"-list[CR]- bitrate and amount of listeners visible and sortable[CR]- 500 Stations on each Page (can be changed in the settings)[CR]- uses cache (24h genre, 1h station listings)</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">With this Add-on you can browse more than 50.000 free internet radio stations. Current Features:[CR]- Top 500 Stations[CR]- Browse by genre (and subgenre if enabled in settings)[CR]- Search Station by name[CR]- Search Stations by current playing track[CR]- You can manage a "My Stations"-list[CR]- bitrate and amount of listeners visible and sortable[CR]- 500 Stations on each Page (can be changed in the settings)[CR]- uses cache (24h genre, 1h station listings)</description>
        <description lang="en_US">With this Add-on you can browse more than 50.000 free internet radio stations. Current Features:[CR]- Top 500 Stations[CR]- Browse by genre (and subgenre if enabled in settings)[CR]- Search Station by name[CR]- Search Stations by current playing track[CR]- You can manage a "My Stations"-list[CR]- bitrate and amount of listeners visible and sortable[CR]- 500 Stations on each Page (can be changed in the settings)[CR]- uses cache (24h genre, 1h station listings)</description>
        <description lang="es">Con este Add-on pueden escucharse más de 50.000 emisoras de radio por Internet gratuitas. Características:[CR]- Las 500 mejores emisoras.[CR]- Búsqueda por género (y por subgéneros si se habilita en la configuración).[CR]- Búsqueda de emisoras por nombre.[CR]- Búsqueda de emisoras que reproducen una canción.[CR]- Posibilidad de administrar un directorio con "Mis emisoras".[CR]- Directorios ordenados que muestran bitrate y cantidad de oyentes.[CR]- 500 emisoras en cada página (la cantidad puede cambiarse en la configuración).[CR]- Uso de caché (24h género, 1h directorio de emisoras).</description>
        <description lang="es_MX">Con este complemento usted puede navegar por mas de 50.000 estaciones de redio de internet gratuitas. Caracteristicas Actuales:[CR]- Mejores 500 Estaciones[CR]- Navegar por genero (y subgenero si lo habilita en los ajustes)[CR]- Busqueda de Estacion por nombre[CR]- Busqueda de Estaciones por la pista actual en reproduccion[CR]- Usted puede administrar una lista"Mis Estaciones"[CR]- tasa de bits y cantidad de oyentes visibles y ordenable[CR]- 500 Estaciones en cada Pagina (puede ser cambiado en los ajustes)[CR]- utiliza cache (24h genero, 1h lista de estaciones)</description>
        <description lang="fr">Avec cette extension vous pouvez accéder à plus de 50.000 station radio internet gratuite. Possibilités actuelles :[CR]- Top 500 stations[CR]- Naviguer par genre (et sous-genre si le réglage est activé)[CR]- Rechercher une station par nom[CR]- Rechercher une station jouant la piste en cours[CR]- Création d'une liste de stations favorites[CR]- Bitrate et nombre d'auditeurs visibles et triables[CR]- 500 stations par page (modifiable dans les réglages)[CR]- Utilisation d'un cache (24h par genre, 1h par station)</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Avec cet addiciel vous pouvez parcourir plus de 50 000 stations de radio Internet gratuites. Caractéristiques actuelles :[CR] - Les 500 1res stations[CR] - Parcourir par genre (et sous-genre si activé dans les paramètres)[CR] - Rechercher les stations par nom[CR] - Rechercher les stations par piste en cours de lecture[CR] - Vous pouvez gérer une liste « Mes stations »[CR] - Débit binaire et nombre d'auditeurs visible et triable[CR] - 500 stations par page (peut être modifié dans les paramètres)[CR] - Utilise un cache (24 h pour les genres, 1h pour les listes de stations).</description>
        <description lang="gl">Grazas a este complemento pode buscar máis de 50.000 emisoras de radio por internet de balde. Características:[CR]- Mellores 500 Emisoras[CR]- Buscar por xénero (e subxénero se esta habilitado na configuración)[CR]- Buscar Emisoras por nome[CR]- Buscar Emisoras pola pista en reprodución actual[CR]- Pode xestionar a listaxe "As miñas Emisoras"[CR]- taxa de bits e número de ointes visíbeis e ordenábel[CR]- 500 Emisoras en cada páxina (pódese trocar na configuración)[CR]- usar a caché (24h para xénero, 1h para listaxe de emisoras)</description>
        <description lang="he">בעזרת הרחבה זו ניתן לעיין ביותר מ-50.000 תחנות רדיו אינטרנטיות חינמיות. כולל:[CR]- 500 התחנות הגדולות ביותר[CR]- עיון לפי סגנון (ותת סגנון אם מאופשר בהגדרות)[CR]- חיפוש תחנה לפי שם[CR]- חיפוש תחנות לפי רצועה המנוגנת כעת[CR]- ניתן לנהל רשימת "התחנות שלי"[CR]- מוצג קצב נתונים וכמות מאזינים וניתן למיין לפיהם[CR]- 500 תחנות בכל עמוד (ניתן לשינוי בהגדרות)[CR]- נעשה שימוש בזיכרון מטמון (24 שע' לסגנונות,1 שע' לרשימת התחנות)</description>
        <description lang="hr">Sa ovim dodatkom možete pregledati više od 50.000 besplatnih Internet radio stanica. Trenutne značajke:[CR]- Top 500 stanica[CR]- Pregledajte prema žanru (i podžanru ako je omogućeno u postavkama)[CR]- Pretraživajte stanice prema nazivu[CR]- Pretraživajte stanice prema trenutnoj reprodukciji pjesme[CR]- Možete upravljati "Moje stanice"-list[CR]- brzina prijenosa i broj slušatelja je vidljiv i prilagodljiv[CR]- 500 stanica na svakoj stranici (mogu se promijeniti u postavkama)[CR]- koristi se predmemorija (24 sata za žanr, 1 sat slušanje stanice)</description>
        <description lang="hu">Ezzel a kiegészítővel választhatsz több mint 50.000 ingyenes rádió adó közül. Jelenlegi szolgáltatások:[CR]- Top 500 állomás[CR]-Műfajonkénti (és alműfajonkénti) keresés[CR]- Név szerinti állomáskeresés[CR]- Állomáskeresés az éppen játszott szám alapján[CR]- Az "én állomásaim" lista kezelése[CR]- Minőség és hallgatottság szerinti rendezés[CR]- 500 adó minden oldalon (a szám beállítható)[CR]- Gyorsítótár használata (24óra a műfajokra, 1óra az állomásokra)</description>
        <description lang="id">Dengan addon ini Anda dapat menjelajahi lebih dari 50.000 stasiun radio gratisan. Fitur saat ini:[CR]- 500 Stasiun Teratas[CR]- Jelajahi berdasarkan tema (dan subtema jika diaktifkan di pengaturan)[CR]- Cari Stasiun berdasarkan nama[CR]- Cari Stasiun berdasarkan trek yang diputar[CR]- Anda dapat mengelola daftar "Stasiun Saya"[CR]- bitrate dan jumlah pendengar terlihat dan dapat diurutkan[CR]- 500 Stasiun setiap halaman (dapat diubah di pengaturan)[CR]- menggunakan cache (24 jam tema, 1 jam daftar stasiun)</description>
        <description lang="it">Con questo Add-on puoi sfogliare più di 50.000 stazioni radio libere su internet. Caratteristiche attuali:[CR]- Migliori 500 stazioni[CR]- Sfoglia per genere (e sottogenere se abilitato nelle impostazioni)[CR]- Cerca le stazioni per nome[CR]- Cerca le stazioni per traccia in esecuzione[CR]- Puoi gestire un lista "Mie Stazioni"[CR]- bitrate e quantità di ascoltatori visibile e riordinabile[CR]- 500 Stazioni in ogni pagina (può essere modificato nelle impostazioni)[CR]- cache utilizzata (24h genere, 1h ascolto)</description>
        <description lang="ko">이 애드온으로 50,000개 이상의 무료 인터넷 라디오 방송을 탐색할 수 있습니다. 현재 기능:[CR]- Top 500 방송국[CR]- 장르(설정에서 활성화하면 하위 장르)로 탐색[CR]- 방송국명으로 검색[CR]- 현재 트랙을 방송중인 방송국 검색[CR]- "내 방송국" 목록 관리[CR]- 비트레이트와 청취자수 표시와 정렬[CR]- 페이지당 500 방송국 표시 (설정에서 변경 가능)[CR]- 캐시 사용 (장르 24시간, 방송국 리스트 1시간)</description>
        <description lang="lt">Su šiuo priedu galite naršyti daugiau kaip 50,000 nemokamų internetinių radijo stočių. Dabartinės funkcijos:[CR]- 500 geriausių stočių[CR]- Naršyti pagal žanrą (ir porūšį, jei įjungta nustatymuose)[CR]- Ieškoti stoties pagal pavadinimą[CR]- Ieškoti stočių pagal dabartinį atkuriamą takelį[CR]- Jūs galite valdyti "Mano radijo stotys" sąrašą[CR]- galima matyti pralaidumą ir klausytojų skaičių bei pagal juos rūšiuoti[CR]- 500 stočių kiekviename puslapyje (galima pakeisti nustatymuose)[CR]- Naudoja talpyklą (24h žanro, 1h stoties sąrašai)</description>
        <description lang="nl">Met deze Add-on die kunt u door meer dan 50.000 vrije internet radiostations bladeren. Huidige functies: [CR]- Top 500 Stations [CR]- bladeren door genre (en subgenre indien ingeschakeld in instellingen) [CR] - Zoek Station op naam [CR] - Zoek Stations door huidig afspelende track [CR]- u kunt een "Mijn Stations" lijst beheren[CR]- bitrate en hoeveelheid luisteraars zichtbaar en sorteerbaar [CR]- 500 Stations op elke pagina (kan gewijzigd worden in de instellingen) [CR]-gebruikte cache (24u genre, 1 uur station luisteren)</description>
        <description lang="no">Med denne utvidelsen kan du finne mer enn 50.000 radiokanaler helt gratis fra internett. Nåværende funksjoner:[CR]- Topp 500 stasjoner[CR]- Bla gjennom etter sjanger (og undersjangre om aktivert i innstillinger)[CR]- Søk etter stasjon med navn[CR]- Søk etter stasjoner etter hva som spilles nå[CR]- Du kan lage din egen "Mine stasjoner" -liste[CR]- Kvalitet og antall lyttere vises og kan filtreres[CR]- 500 stasjoner på hver side (kan endres i innstillinger)[CR]- Bruker mellomlagring (24 timer for sjanger, 1 time for stasjonslister)</description>
        <description lang="pl">Dzięki tej wtyczce możesz przeglądać w ponad 50.000 darmowych stacjach radiowych. Aktualne funkcje:[CR]- Top 500 stacji[CR]- przeglądaj według gatunków (oraz subgatunków jeżeli włączone)[CR]- szukaj stacji po nazwie[CR]- szukaj stacji po granym utworze[CR]- zarządzaj listą Moje stacje[CR]- sortowanie oraz widoczność liczby słuchaczy i bitrate[CR]- 500 stacji na stronie (możliwa edycja)[CR]- pamięć podręczna (24h gatunki, 1h lista stacji)</description>
        <description lang="pt">Com este add-on, pode escolher entre mais de 50.000 estações de rádio da net grátis. Funcionalidades:[CR]- Top 500 Rádios[CR]- Procure por Género (e sub-género, se activo nas preferências)[CR]- Procurar Rádio por nome[CR]- Procurar Rádios por faixa em reprodução[CR]- Pode gerir uma lista de "Minhas Rádios"[CR]- bitrate e quantidade de ouvintes visíveis e ordenáveis[CR]- 500 Rádios em cada Página (pode ser alterado nas preferências)[CR]- usar cache (24h para género, 1h para lista das rádios)</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Com este Add-on, você pode navegar em mais de 50.000 estações de rádio on-line grátis. Características atuais:[CR]- As 500 Melhores Estações[CR]- Procurar por gênero (e subgênero se habilitado nas configurações)[CR]- Pesquisar estações por nome[CR]- Pesquisar estações pela faixa atual[CR]- Você pode gerenciar uma lista de "Minhas Estações"[CR]- bitrate e quantidade de ouvintes visíveis e ordenáveis[CR]- 500 estações por página (pode ser alterado nas configurações)[CR]- usa cache (24h para gêneros, 1h para listagem de estações)</description>
        <description lang="ru">С этим дополнением Вы сможете слушать более 50 тысяч доступных свободных радиостанций. На данный момент плагин позволяет:[CR]- Просматривать Top 500 станций[CR]- Искать по стилю (и подстилю, если задано в настройках)[CR]- Искать станции по имени[CR]- Искать похожие станции по текущей воспроизводимой музыке[CR]- Управление списком "Мои станции"[CR]- Просматривать, сортировать по битрейту и количеству слушателей[CR]- 500 станций на каждой странице (может быть изменено в настройках)[CR]- Использование кеширования (стили на 24 часа, списки станций на 1 час) </description>
        <description lang="sk">S týmto doplnok môžete prehliadať vyše 50.000 voľných internetových rádio staníc. Momentálne podporuje:&#10;- Top 500 staníc&#10;- Prehliadanie podľa žánru (a pod-žánru, ak povolené v nastaveniach)&#10;- hľadanie stanice podľa mena&#10;- hľadanie stanice podľa práve hranej skladby&#10;- Môžete spravovať zoznam "Moje stanice"&#10;- zobrazenie a zoradenie podľa dátového toku a počtu poslucháčov&#10;- 500 staníc na každej strane (môže byť zmenené v nastaveniach)&#10;- používa medzi-pamäť (24h pre žánre, 1h pre zoznam staníc)</description>
        <description lang="sv">Med detta tillägg kan du bläddra bland mer än 50.000 fria internetradiostationer. Nuvarande funktioner:[CR]- Topp 500 stationer[CR]- Bläddra efter genre (och undergenre, om det är påslaget i inställningar)[CR]- Sök station efter namn[CR]- Sök stationer som spelar låt[CR]- Du kan hantera "Mina stationer"-lista[CR]- bitrate och antal lyssnare är synligt och sorterbart[CR]- 500 stationer på varje sida (kan ändras i inställningar)[CR]- använder buffert (24 genre, 1 timmes stationlista)</description>
        <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த துணை பயன் மூலம் நீங்கள் 50.000 மேற்பட்ட இலவச இணைய வானொலி நிலையங்களை உலாவ முடியும். தற்போதய சிறப்பியல்:[CR]- உச்சி 500 நிலையங்கள்[CR]- வகைபடி உலாவு (துணை வகைப்படி சேர்க்கவும் - அமைப்புகளில் தேர்வு செய்யவும்)[CR]- பெயர்படி நிலையத்தனி தேடுக[CR]- பெயர்படி நிலையத்தனி தேடுக[CR]- "என்னுடைய நிலையங்கள்" பட்டியலை நீங்கள் நிர்வகிக்க முடியும்[CR]- பிட்வீதம் மற்றும் கேட்போர் அளவுகளை பார்க்கவும் மற்றும் வரிசைபடுத்தவும்[CR]- ஒரு பக்கத்தில் 500 நிலையங்கள் (அமைப்புகளில் மாற்ற இயலும்)[CR]- தேக்கத்தை பயன்படுத்தவும் (24 மணிநேர வகை, 1 மணிநேர நிலைய பட்டியல்)</description>
        <description lang="zh">你可以使用本插件浏览超过50.000免费网络电台。当前功能：[CR]- 500强电台[CR]- 按类别浏览（可设置子类）[CR]- 按名字搜索电台[CR]- 按当前播放曲目搜索电台[CR]- 管理“我的电台”-列表[CR]- 按比特率和收听人数排序[CR]- 每页500个电台（可设置）[CR]- 使用缓存（24小时类别，1小时站点列表）</description>
    </extension>
</addon>
