<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.greenpeace" name="Greenpeace videos" version="1.1.4" provider-name="Jose Antonio Montes (jamontes)">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="3.4.4"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.vimeo" version="2.5.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en">Greenpeace Videos.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Greenpeace is an independent global campaigning organisation that acts since 1971 to change attitudes and behaviour, to protect and conserve the environment and to promote the peace in a non-violent manner. To maintain its independence, Greenpeace does not accept donations from governments or corporations but relies on contributions from individual supporters and foundation grants.[CR]This add-on allows to watch the Greenpeace videos available online through their websites around the world.</description>
        <summary lang="es">Greenpeace Vídeos.</summary>
        <description lang="es">Greenpeace es una organización independiente global, que actúa desde 1971 para cambiar actitudes y comportamientos, proteger y conservar el medio ambiente, y promover la paz, de forma no violenta. Para mantener su independencia, Greenpeace no acepta donaciones de gobiernos, empresas, ni partidos políticos, sino que depende de las aportaciones de sus socios.[CR]Este add-on permite ver los vídeos online de Greenpeace, disponibles en sus sitios web alrededor del mundo.</description>
        <language>bg cs da de el en es fi fr hi in it iw ja ko nl no pt ro ru sl sv th tr zh</language>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=167903</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/jamontes/plugin.video.greenpeace</source>
    </extension>
</addon>
